Twenty years ago,
the Dragon-Seeking Zhang Family
led The Four Great Families of Wan-Mei-Qi-Sheng
to Wanglong Mountain
and found a moving Tidal Tomb.
That was a once-in-a-century grand tomb!
But after that, the Dragon-Seeking Lineage vanished.
And bizarre events started piling up.
Cousin,
did you bring our Qi family's Ghost-Suppressing Talisman?
Cousin, why use a butcher's knife on a chicken?
Tiankun,
light a candle in the southwest corner.
Let everyone witness our Qi family's
authentic Ghost-Inquiring Door-Knocking.
Alright.
Left on Azure Dragon to seek the tomb eye.
Right on White Tiger to set the gate.
Open!
Let's go, everyone.
Did I get it backwards?
Right on Azure Dragon to seek the tomb eye.
Left on White Tiger to set the gate.
Open again!
Don't be afraid, I'm here.
Zhang Tianyou, what are you doing?
Seal of Qian, Bearing Heaven. Awaken the spirit of Tianshu!
Earth, respond and uphold. Shake the earth's axis!
Spells open the mystic gate. Let the tomb door open!
Young Master Qi.
This door...
opens inward.
I've raided countless tombs since I was a kid.
How could I not know this door opens inward?
Move aside, move aside, move aside!
Tiankun, mind your manners.
Let's go.
Cousin, why is there a corridor behind this door?
That's how it should be.
From my experience raiding tombs with my family,
this means there's a code to this trade.
But,
we usually have a rooster scout ahead for us.
Brother,
we don't have a rooster,
but we can make do with a useless fool.
Cousin,
how about your man scouts ahead for us?
Zhang Tianyou, you're my husband.
Walk in front and protect me.
Don't embarrass our Sheng family.
Ling Yu, I've heard
that ghosts usually appear from behind.
I'm afraid...
Brother, did you hear that?
This guy's probably wet his pants in fear.
Acting like this, he still wants to be the Sheng family son-in-law?
It's a Step-String Trap.
Fine.
Then don't regret it.
Excuse me.
You...
Young Master Qi.
This is the solution to the Seven-Star Steps.
Such a basic trap
should be a piece of cake for you, right?
Hey, just a friendly reminder.
One wrong step and you'll be shot full of holes.
Such a basic trap,
I'm sure you two won't have any problems.
Then, Cousin, we'll go wait for you up ahead.
Yeah.
You dirty rat, just you wait!
Left one, right two.
Left three, right four, left five, right six.
Then right seven.
Hmm.
Easy.
Brother,
I feel like
something is touching me from behind.
Brother!
Oh, don't be scared.
It's just touching you.
It wouldn't dare touch me.
Brother!
Tianyou, protect me!
Don't worry.
Looks like I'll have to use my Qi family's Amulet
to show this monster a thing or two.
Done.
Why isn't this talisman working?
What are you doing?
Hey, stay back!
Why are you chasing me?!
Ah! Why are you only chasing me?!
Tiankun!
Why isn't the Amulet working anymore?
My brother's...
Dao Heart is broken.
Don't come any closer!
Why are you only chasing me?!
Help!
Move!
The wonders of Yin-Yang Reversal are endless.
Two extremes return to the Nine Palaces.
Freeze!
Smells so good!
Baby,
My little darling
Baby
Cousin,
Have you always wanted to marry me?
Ling Yu,
What just happened?
I had my eyes closed the whole time.
I didn't see anything.
Then you missed a lot of excitement.
I've already subdued that female ghost.
Right over there.
She just knelt before me.
Cousin, that scared me to death just now.
I was just waiting for the Amulet to take effect.
If this kid hadn't gotten in the way,
I would've beaten that female ghost till her Soul scattered.
Bro.
So that's how it is.
Your tactical screaming just now
almost fooled even me.
Cousin, you're amazing.
That's why I told you,
that's why I told you,
trivial matters like this
can't stop our Qi family.
You need to stay calm from now on.
Don't get scared to death so easily.
Let's go.
Let me borrow this.
Hey, I saw it.
It's fine.
I saw it.
That female ghost was kneeling to you.
You saw it?
I saw it.